This is number five of my five favorite
Buy for Life items. This is the rOtring
>> [music]
>> 800. What I like about these pens is
that they have super high build quality.
So, they're completely made out of metal
and it has a retractable tip. [music]
The reason why this retractable tip is
very nice is because you can just throw
this in your backpack [music]
or into a sling, for example, without
worrying that it's going to snap off. In
the case with a pen, you don't have to
worry about it bleeding or it marking up
stuff in your backpack. I first got the
rOtring 800 in a stationery shop in
Taiwan when I was in high school and it
has been one of my favorite mechanical
pencils of all time. These pens [music]
definitely come at a premium price. I
think they're about $50, but I think
it's pretty underrated as someone who's
been journaling [music] for 10 years to
buy a high-quality pen or pencil.
Because when you have a high-quality pen
or pencil, it's [music] kind of like
having a high-end guitar. It makes you
want to play more. It makes you want to
journal more. And so, you end up doing
the thing that you wanted [music] to do
more.